ABDERRAHIM NABAOUI

UNITY GAME DEVELOPER

- +212637852855 @ nabaoui.abderrahim@gmail.com Agadir, Morocco
- https://www.gamox.ma/portfolio

Profile

Unity game programmer with over 8 years of experience in programming and problem solving, 5 years in web/mobile development, and 3 years in the gaming field. In 2020 I launched my start-up Gamox (Gamox.ma) to get in touch with other hyper-casual studios. and recently I worked with 9tales (9tales.io) to release their NFT demo card game.

Professional Experience

Unity Game Developer

- www.9tales.io **9tales**
- Create <u>9tales demo NFT card game</u>.
- Transform 100% of design specification into functional games.

2021 - 2022

- Implement some of the game 3D models and VFX.
- Communicate with other 3 team members.

Gamox CEO

- **2020 2022** R Gamox www.gamox.ma
- Work on hyper-casual mobile games from scratch in Unity 3D.
- Collaboration with Moonee studio publisher on 3 hyper-casual games, (Brain Master 3D, Stack Crowds Running 3D, Stack Crowds Running 3D)

1337 School Projects

- 2016 - 2018 **h** 1337
- Make a small Ray tracing rendering engine with C language, supporting mirror effect, transparency, texture application and more.
- Recreate <u>Shadowmatic</u> full game from scratch in unity 3D.

Project Manager

- www.fikralabs.com **Fikralabs 2016 - 2018**
- Develop a Platform web to announce used cars for sell.
- Create 3 websites: Fikralabs, Hotel Targante, If-company.
- Municipality of Lqliaa website

Education

Information Technology Architect (Computer Graphic)

1337 Coding School

2018 - 2022

Associate Degree in web Development and Multimedia (Web Development)

EWA School Agadir

2013 - 2015

Two Years in Faculty Option Physics (Physics)

Science Faculty IBN ZOHR (FSA)

2011 - 2013

Professional Skills

HTML/CSS Unity 3D

Adobe Photoshop Blender

Achievement

Speaker @ DevFest Agadir

GDG Agadir

12/2019 Agadir

Flutter Workshop.

Participation @ Google for MENA Summit

Google

12/2019 Dubai

Summit for all Google Developers Leaders organised by Google in Dubai.

Participation @ AiHackTunisia

Google and InstaDeep

1 09/2019 Tunisia

Intelligence Artificielle Hackathon organised by Google and InstaDeep in Tunisia.

1337 Game Jam

1337

© 02/2019 Khouribga

Game about Women's day theme.

Portfolio

- https://github.com/azertfx
- https://www.behance.net/azertfx
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/abderrahimnabaoui

Languages

Arabic Native

English Intermediate

French Intermediate